

NAUSHIKHA JAYAWICKRAMA

Phone: +94 76331 6991

E-mail: hello@naushikha.com

Website: naushikha.com

COMPUTER ENTHUSIAST

PROFILE

Hardworking, self-motivated ambitious programmer with a keen eye for detail. Excellent track record of performance in all tasks undertaken with nearly 3 years of cumulative industrial working experience in fields such as game testing, networking, customer support and tutoring.

Aiming to work in a challenging but friendly environment with a goal to become a part of a team.

EXPERIENCE

PLAYTESTER

Arimac (Jan 2021 - May 2021)

• Testing and evaluating Android mobile games

VIRTUAL INTERN

Nestlé (Oct 2020 - Dec 2020)

Researching for the supply-chain division to localize use of raw materials

SYSTEM ENGINEER

Telasis Solutions (2017 - 2019)

- System and network installation and administration
- Server and desktop hardware configuration

VIRTUAL ASSISTANT

Voigue (Dec 2017 - Jan 2018)

 Support team services to handle Daraz.lk's excess user traffic during Christmas

INTERN

Third Space Global (Dec 2016 - Jan 2017)

• Online tutoring mathematics for school children stationed in the UK

SKILLS

- Linux, networking and system administration
- WebGL graphics and web design
- Hardware installation, upgrading and maintennance
- Quick learning
- Problem solving
- Adaptability
- Fluent communication

EDUCATION

BSC (HONS) COMPUTER SCIENCE

University of Colombo School of Computing (2019 >>)

• Current GPA: 3.8

0/L, A/L

Ananda College, Colombo 10. (2003 - 2016)

• Ordinary Level : 9 As

• Advanced Level: Z-Score - 2.3634, Island Rank - 8, District Rank - 2







ADDITIONAL INFO

Stated below is a list of projects I have done on my own or developed with the help of a team. These are selected primarily on the basis that they are very closely related to the domain of graphics, game development or simulation.

PROJECTS

WHEN ONCE THE SKY WAS BLUE

Immersive 360° Web Experience - 2021

- Designed using Three.js, pure HTML, CSS and JS.
- Built to showcase at the Women's Theatre Festival '21- "WTFRINGE21".
- Completed entire experience within a short span of 2 weeks.
 <u>Trailer Link</u> | Request for Demo

VACCINE HUNT

2D Side Scrolling Platformer - 2021

- Made with a team for the Global Game Jam 2021 using Unity.
- Was in charge of lighting, sound design and some bug fixing.
 Download Link

HARD DUOS

1vs1 Multiplayer Attacker-Defender Game - 2019

- Made with a team for the IEEE GameRush Hackathon 2019 using Unreal.
- 2nd runner up in the competition.
- Was overseeing sound design and presentation.
 Presentation Link

TEST ARENA

3D First Person Shooter - 2017

- Designed using Visual Basic 6.0, DirectX 8 and TrueVision3D.
- Personal project to explore boundaries of VB6 + TV3D.
 Write-up Link | Demo Video

COMMAND ATTACK 3

3D First Person Shooter - 2012

- Designed using Visual Basic 6.0, DirectX 8 and TrueVision3D.
- Built to showcase at the "Anada Abhiman" exhibition of Ananda College.
- Completed 2 levels for the game in 2 weeks, including story, cutscenes and gameplay mechanics.
 Write-up Link

REFERENCES

AIR CDRE (RETD) JAYASIRI AMARASENA CEO

Sri Lanka CERT|CC ceo@cert.gov.lk | 077 452 4144

DR. MANJUSRI WICKRAMASINGHE

Senior Lecturer

B.Sc Hons in CS (col), PhD (Monash)
University of Colombo School of Computing

mie@ucsc.cmb.ac.lk | 071 316 8483

HIMARUK SILVA

Software Engineer

SimCentric Technologies

himaruks@simct.com | 077 540 1352





